[Music]
the aunt and the Dove once upon a time a
very thirsty aunt was drinking water
from the river suddenly the aunt lost
his balance and fell into the river
water help help help
cried the aunt but no one could hear his
cries a dove sitting on a tree nearby
saw that the aunt was in trouble she
quickly plucked off a leaf from the tree
and dropped it into the water the aunt
climbed on the leaf he thanked the Dove
for saving his life after a few days the
Dove was sitting on a tree the aunt saw
hunter painting his arrow record of the
aunt knew that his friend the Dove was
in danger fit the hunters leg
the hunter cried in pain
[Music]
the hunters arrow missed the death this
time the aunt saved the Dove the Dove
thanked the ad for saving her life and
they became friends forever moral of the
story one good deed deserves another
[Music]
[Applause]